[{"answer": "In the sight of God that is a sin", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Do you understand that you have sinned? Gravely", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Do you understand that you have sinned? Gravely", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I cannot leave alone a soul in pain", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Why? People fart backwards", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yes, I think it's brilliant. You've been doing it for years", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh, ha, ha, ha", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes, you are. You're very sick", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Exactly", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well not especially. It can be in Turkish, if you really want. I don't care", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Let us pass, please! Let us pass at once! We're with the Emperor", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Do you know who I am?  This is my daughter. I am my friend. We are favoured guests", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, I mean occasionally it seems to have, how shall one say?  How shall one say, Director", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Exactly. Very well put. Too many notes", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "my friend, you are not the only composer in that place", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "A little modesty would suit you better", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well, don't do that again", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Don't be stupid", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Pupils", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Yes", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "There's a young girl to see you", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Did you not know that His Majesty has expressly forbidden ballet in his operas", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Exactly. A dance", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, I can speak for the Emperor. You made too many demands on the royal ear. The poor man can't concentrate for more than an hour and you gave him four", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I think it's marvelous. Truly", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "It's the best opera yet written. I know it! Why didn't they come", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I know, I know. Perhaps you should give me some lessons in that", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Oh no, the honour would be all mine", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Grazie, a lei, my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Well, you liked it, didn't you? Monke", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Stanz", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Half the house! You'll never see a penny. I want it here, in my hand", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Shut up! I'll not let you put anything in my hand until I see some money", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "What work", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "What dead? Who is dead", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Oh no. It is a sublime piece. The grandest operone. I tell you, you are the greatest composer known to me", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I do", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "The Fire", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Common time", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Why? Why? Why? Why add to your misery by confessing to murder? You didn't kill him", "docId": "Amadeus.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "No, you didn't", "qsentId": 42}]